I want your cock in my mouth, I want you
to push my head down until your cock hits
the
back of my throat.
I wanna feel you get hard against my
tongue, your
fist in my hair, your hips, thrust in my
lips
around your cock, I'm gagging, I'm
drooling.
I wanna taste you, wanna swallow, I wanna
make you
come
And then I want you to flip me over and
push your cock inside my cunt And fuck me
until
I can't think, don't stop harder
Your cock inside my cunt, your hand around
my throat
Your other hand on my clit.
I'm coming, I'm coming.ing My cunt clench
around you in
waves, I'm so wet.
You can feel it, you can hear it.
Every thrust, slick and dip.
I want you to come inside me, I wanna feel
your pulse. I want your cock buried deep
in my
cunt when I come.
You pin my wrist above my head, you spread
my
legs. Your cock pushes in, I'm so wet,
there's no
resistance. You thrust deep, hard, your
hips slamming into me.
You're cock hitting the spot inside me
that makes my
whole body shake my thighs.
Trembling, my cunt gripping you.
You pull my hair, you tell me to look at
you. I look, you tell me not to come yet.
I'm trying, I can.
I come around your cock, and you feel me
smile.
You don't stop.
My cunt is yours, my mouth is yours.
I want your cock in every part of me.
I wanna come three times: once on your
tongue, once
on your cock, once with your fingers
inside me.
I want you to use me, I want you to
take me. I wanna feel your come inside my
cunt.
I wanna taste you on my lips, I want it
all. Failure first, AI
safety research. Failure first.